<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Projects on Stacy Scudder</title>
    <link>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Projects on Stacy Scudder</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Paranormal Playlist</title>
      <link>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/project-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/project-1/</guid>
      <description>About
This is a recommender system that lets you enter a paranormal romance book and get back a list of 20 hair metal songs as a soundtrack. I looked around for an app or website that would let a reader create a playlist based on a book, but there weren&amp;rsquo;t any. Every recommender I found stayed within the same mediums: book to book, music to music, etc. So I thought I&amp;rsquo;d have some fun and create my own.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Library</title>
      <link>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/project-2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/project-2/</guid>
      <description>This project will incorporate pieces from several other repos dealing with book data to build a personal library.
About
I have a large personal library that includes books, ebooks, and audiobooks. For several years, I&amp;rsquo;ve used a free program called Calibre to manage my ebooks. Recently, I&amp;rsquo;ve thought about including my audiobooks and physical books, as well, but I&amp;rsquo;m still trying to find the best way to include everything I want.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Predicting the NBA MVP</title>
      <link>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/project-3/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://stacyscudder.github.io/post/project-3/</guid>
      <description>About
My grandson asked me about setting up a webpage or app with a dashboard for NCAA or NBA stats. I wanted to be able to show him how to scrape the stats and use it to make predictions before moving on to the dashboard, but I needed more practice myself before teaching him.
Data
For this project, I scraped data from basketball-reference since it had a table with MVP data that was easier to scrape.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
